question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Leonardo da Vinci&#039;s Mona Lisa does not have eyebrows.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The full English name of the car manufacturer BMW is Bavarian Motor Works",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and "
                 "the Gamecube remake.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Linux was first created as an alternative to Windows XP.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
